aquarist-classifieds.co.uk 2019-08-17

# PRIVACY STATEMENT Aquarist Classified Adverts

We are committed to the privacy of our visitors. We collect no personal information about you when you visit our Web site unless you choose to provide that information to us.

Information Collected and Stored Automatically: If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the Web site, read pages or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store information that is used for traffic analysis, such as the route by which you arrived at our website and pages visited.

We do not collect sensitive personal information without your consent. Consent is assumed if you complete a form to register with Aquarist Classifieds for the purposes of submitting, editing,or removing an advertisment.

Cookies: These are small bits of text that are either used for the duration of a browser session, or saved on a user's hard drive in order to identify that user, or information about that user, the next time the user logs on to a Web site. Such are used to log back into the site for future visits.

You can choose not to accept cookies and still use our Web site. However, you will be unable to use the cookie-dependent features, such as adding, editing and deleting your advertisments. Refer to the help information in your browser software for instructions on how to disable cookies.

We do not disclose, give, sell or transfer any personal information about our visitors, unless required for law enforcement or statute.

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy at this location.
